const quizDataFromFile = [
  {
    "question": "böse",
    "correct": "angry",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "female",
      "angry",
      "sharp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "falsch",
    "correct": "wrong / incorrect",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "wrong / incorrect",
      "possible",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "glücklich",
    "correct": "happily",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "male",
      "happily",
      "small"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "groß",
    "correct": "tall",
    "choices": [
      "wrong / incorrect",
      "large",
      "tall",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "groß",
    "correct": "large",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "large",
      "angry",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gut",
    "correct": "good",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "punctual",
      "right / correct",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gut",
    "correct": "good",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "happily",
      "green",
      "angry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gut",
    "correct": "good",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "green",
      "tall",
      "small"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gut",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "black",
      "wrong / incorrect",
      "…",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gut",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "possible",
      "…",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hell",
    "correct": "light",
    "choices": [
      "angry",
      "red",
      "…",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "herzlich",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "happily",
      "large",
      "…",
      "blue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "klein",
    "correct": "small",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "black",
      "female",
      "small"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "männlich",
    "correct": "male",
    "choices": [
      "male",
      "happily",
      "green",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "möglich",
    "correct": "possible",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "possible",
      "angry",
      "correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "neu",
    "correct": "new",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "black",
      "wrong / incorrect",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "neu",
    "correct": "new",
    "choices": [
      "wrong / incorrect",
      "blue",
      "large",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pünktlich",
    "correct": "sharp",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "new",
      "happily",
      "sharp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pünktlich",
    "correct": "punctual",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "punctual",
      "large",
      "red"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "richtig",
    "correct": "correct",
    "choices": [
      "punctual",
      "sharp",
      "white",
      "correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "richtig",
    "correct": "right / correct",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "black",
      "right / correct",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weiblich",
    "correct": "female",
    "choices": [
      "happily",
      "green",
      "female",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schwarz",
    "correct": "black",
    "choices": [
      "black",
      "right / correct",
      "wrong / incorrect",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "blau",
    "correct": "blue",
    "choices": [
      "new",
      "possible",
      "female",
      "blue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "grün",
    "correct": "green",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "white",
      "green",
      "sharp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weiß",
    "correct": "white",
    "choices": [
      "possible",
      "white",
      "red",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "rot",
    "correct": "red",
    "choices": [
      "new",
      "punctual",
      "red",
      "correct"
    ]
  }
];